Contact

kevinplaut@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kevin-plaut (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Software Quality Assurance Test Automation Leadership

Certifications

Teaching Kids Programming Instructor

Kevin Plaut

Quality Assurance Lead at PickTrace

Oceanside

Summary

Quality Assurance Engineering Manager skilled in automated testing and financial technology with over 10 years of experience leading and mentoring teams; and a strong passion for software development and building experiences that people will love.

Experience

PickTrace
Quality Assurance Lead
October 2020 - Present (7 months)

Procore Technologies
4 years 8 months

Manager, QA Engineering

October 2019 - September 2020 (1 year) San Diego, California, United States

Lead QA Engineer July 2018 - October 2019 (1 year 4 months) Carpinteria, CA

QA Engineer & Scrum Master February 2016 - July 2018 (2 years 6 months) Carpinteria, CA

RMIS | Registry Monitoring Insurance Services QA & Technical Support Engineer October 2015 - February 2016 (5 months) Westlake Village, CA

Richner Communications
General Manager, Operations
November 2010 - March 2015 (4 years 5 months)
Garden City, NY

Et al.

...

January 2000 - October 2010 (10 years 10 months)

Education

Brooks Institute

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) · (2006 - 2009)